{"facts": ["They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Ivan, Theodora, Peter.", "Peter is at house 4.", "Ivan is at house 3.", "Elena lives next door from Ivan."], "question": "Who is at house 1?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Ivan", "Theodora", "Peter"], "answer": "Theodora", "seed": 1729293458674}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Theodora, Peter.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Elena is at house 4.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 3.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a zebra.", "Theodora owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a hamster."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Ivan?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293459245}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Theodora, Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Elena owns a zebra.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives next door from the one who is is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a zebra.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a snake.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives next door from the one who is owns a snake.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in red clothes"], "answer": "is in yellow clothes", "seed": 1729293460056}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Elena, Peter.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 also is the criminal.", "Theodora owns a snake.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a snake.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Theodora.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a cat.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "Ivan owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in red clothes."], "question": "Who is at house 4?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Theodora", "Elena", "Peter"], "answer": "Theodora", "seed": 1729293461959}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Theodora, Elena.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in green clothes.", "Theodora lives 2 doors away from Elena.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a snake.", "Peter owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a snake.", "Ivan is the criminal.", "Elena is in green clothes."], "question": "What pet does Theodora own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a cat", "owns a zebra", "owns a snake"], "answer": "owns a zebra", "seed": 1729293463425}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "The person who is owns a snake lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a zebra.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["is at house 2", "is at house 3", "is at house 1", "is at house 4"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293464819}
{"facts": ["They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena, Theodora.", "Ivan is at house 2.", "Peter lives next door from Elena."], "question": "Who is at house 1?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Peter", "Elena", "Theodora"], "answer": "Theodora", "seed": 1729293467089}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also is the criminal.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a hamster.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a zebra."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a hamster?", "answer_options": ["is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in yellow clothes"], "answer": "is in yellow clothes", "seed": 1729293467926}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives next door from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a snake."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in blue clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a cat", "owns a hamster", "owns a snake", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293468825}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives next door from the one who is owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in red clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a zebra."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 1 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a hamster", "owns a snake", "owns a cat"], "answer": "owns a zebra", "seed": 1729293470559}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Theodora, Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 3.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is owns a snake lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Elena owns a snake.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "Ivan is at house 2."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Theodora", "Elena", "Peter", "Ivan"], "answer": "Elena", "seed": 1729293472099}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a hamster.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also owns a cat."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a snake?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293474877}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan, Theodora.", "Peter owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a snake.", "Elena is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in red clothes.", "Theodora is at house 2."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Ivan?", "answer_options": ["is in yellow clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293476265}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a zebra."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a snake", "owns a cat", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293477283}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Theodora, Ivan.", "Peter is in green clothes.", "Theodora owns a snake.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in red clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 also is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "Elena owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a zebra."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a hamster?", "answer_options": ["is in yellow clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in red clothes"], "answer": "is in green clothes", "seed": 1729293479114}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in blue clothes."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is in yellow clothes?", "answer_options": ["is at house 3", "is at house 2", "is at house 1", "is at house 4"], "answer": "is at house 2", "seed": 1729293480422}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Elena, Peter.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a snake.", "Peter is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Elena lives 2 doors away from Peter.", "Theodora is at house 4.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives next door from the one who is owns a cat.", "The person who is owns a cat lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a zebra."], "question": "What pet does Elena own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a snake", "owns a cat", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293482199}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a snake.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Theodora, Elena.", "Ivan lives next door from Theodora.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a snake.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 4.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 4.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a snake."], "question": "Who is at house 3?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Ivan", "Theodora", "Elena"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293483437}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a hamster."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["is in yellow clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293484959}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Theodora, Elena, Ivan.", "Theodora lives next door from Elena.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in green clothes.", "Theodora is at house 1.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a snake.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 also is the criminal."], "question": "Who is in red clothes?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Theodora", "Elena", "Ivan"], "answer": "Elena", "seed": 1729293485822}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Theodora, Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a cat.", "Theodora is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a cat.", "Elena isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal."], "question": "What pet does Peter own?", "answer_options": ["owns a snake", "owns a hamster", "owns a cat", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293486794}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a cat.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Elena.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 1.", "Theodora is at house 4.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a zebra.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in blue clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a snake?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in yellow clothes"], "answer": "is in yellow clothes", "seed": 1729293487756}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Elena, Peter.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Peter.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Peter owns a hamster.", "Theodora is at house 1.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in blue clothes.", "The person who is owns a cat lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a zebra."], "question": "Who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Theodora", "Elena", "Peter"], "answer": "Theodora", "seed": 1729293489088}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a zebra.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in red clothes."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is in blue clothes?", "answer_options": ["is at house 4", "is at house 1", "is at house 2", "is at house 3"], "answer": "is at house 2", "seed": 1729293490238}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Elena, Peter.", "Elena lives next door from Peter.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a snake.", "Theodora lives next door from Elena.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a snake.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a snake."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is in green clothes?", "answer_options": ["is at house 1", "is at house 2", "is at house 3", "is at house 4"], "answer": "is at house 1", "seed": 1729293491402}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Theodora, Ivan, Elena.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a snake.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 2.", "Theodora isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Ivan lives next door from Elena.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a snake.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a cat.", "Theodora lives next door from Ivan.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "Theodora owns a zebra.", "Theodora is in blue clothes."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a cat", "owns a zebra", "owns a hamster", "owns a snake"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293493232}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Theodora, Elena, Ivan, Peter.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 3.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 2.", "Ivan owns a cat.", "Peter is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 also is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a cat.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a snake."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who owns a hamster?", "answer_options": ["is at house 2", "is at house 1", "is at house 4", "is at house 3"], "answer": "is at house 1", "seed": 1729293494967}
{"facts": ["They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan, Theodora.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Peter is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 4.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 3.", "Elena lives next door from Theodora."], "question": "Which is the house of Ivan?", "answer_options": ["is at house 2", "is at house 3", "is at house 4", "is at house 1"], "answer": "is at house 4", "seed": 1729293496412}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena, Theodora.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a snake.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a zebra.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Peter is in blue clothes."], "question": "Who owns a hamster?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Ivan", "Elena", "Theodora"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293497685}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Theodora, Peter, Ivan.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 3.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Theodora", "Peter", "Ivan"], "answer": "Theodora", "seed": 1729293498701}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan, Theodora.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 2.", "Ivan is in yellow clothes.", "Peter is in red clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a zebra."], "question": "Which is the house of Theodora?", "answer_options": ["is at house 4", "is at house 3", "is at house 1", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 2", "seed": 1729293499714}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Theodora, Peter.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a snake.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in green clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 4.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Peter.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 2.", "Theodora is in red clothes."], "question": "What pet does Peter own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a cat", "owns a snake", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293501091}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Peter, Theodora.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a snake.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a zebra.", "Ivan owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 2 also is the criminal.", "The person who is owns a cat lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra."], "question": "Who is in green clothes?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Elena", "Peter", "Theodora"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293502796}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a zebra.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Ivan, Peter, Theodora.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 1.", "Elena lives 2 doors away from Ivan.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a hamster.", "Theodora is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal."], "question": "What pet does Elena own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a cat", "owns a snake", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293504489}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Theodora, Ivan.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Ivan is at house 4.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in red clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 2.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a zebra.", "Elena is at house 1.", "Ivan isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a cat.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a cat."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a zebra", "owns a cat", "owns a snake"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293505301}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "The person who is owns a snake lives next door from the one who is owns a cat.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a hamster.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a hamster."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is at house 1?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293506644}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Peter, Elena, Ivan.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in green clothes.", "Peter owns a hamster.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in red clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 3.", "Theodora lives next door from Peter.", "Theodora owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a cat."], "question": "Who owns a snake?", "answer_options": ["Theodora", "Peter", "Elena", "Ivan"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293507855}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Ivan, Peter, Theodora.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in blue clothes.", "Theodora is at house 1.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a cat.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 4.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "Elena owns a zebra."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in yellow clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a cat", "owns a snake", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293509313}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena, Theodora.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also owns a snake.", "Peter isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 1.", "Elena isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 4.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a cat.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Elena."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is at house 4?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in yellow clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293510368}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in red clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a snake.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "Elena is in red clothes.", "Theodora lives next door from Peter.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a cat."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in yellow clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a cat", "owns a hamster", "owns a snake"], "answer": "owns a zebra", "seed": 1729293511811}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a snake.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "Peter is in blue clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a snake.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a zebra.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 2.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 2."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["is at house 3", "is at house 2", "is at house 4", "is at house 1"], "answer": "is at house 2", "seed": 1729293514520}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Theodora, Elena.", "Ivan is in red clothes.", "Theodora owns a cat.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in red clothes.", "The person who is owns a cat lives next door from the one who is owns a hamster.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a snake."], "question": "Who owns a hamster?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Peter", "Theodora", "Elena"], "answer": "Elena", "seed": 1729293516088}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Theodora, Peter, Ivan.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Theodora is at house 3.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a hamster.", "Theodora lives 2 doors away from Peter."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Theodora", "Peter", "Ivan"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293517207}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a snake.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "Theodora owns a hamster.", "Elena is at house 3.", "Ivan owns a snake.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a snake."], "question": "Who is at house 1?", "answer_options": ["Theodora", "Elena", "Peter", "Ivan"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293518970}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "Theodora owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Peter owns a hamster.", "Theodora is at house 2.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in green clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a snake?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in green clothes", "seed": 1729293519833}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Theodora, Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Ivan owns a snake.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is owns a cat lives next door from the one who is owns a hamster.", "Theodora lives next door from Ivan.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Theodora is at house 1."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a snake", "owns a cat", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a zebra", "seed": 1729293521142}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Theodora, Peter.", "Peter isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Elena lives next door from Peter.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "Peter is at house 4.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in blue clothes."], "question": "Who is in yellow clothes?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Elena", "Theodora", "Peter"], "answer": "Elena", "seed": 1729293523153}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a snake.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a snake.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 4.", "Peter lives 2 doors away from Ivan.", "Peter owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a zebra."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 1 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a cat", "owns a zebra", "owns a snake"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293524263}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in blue clothes.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a cat."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a hamster?", "answer_options": ["is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in yellow clothes"], "answer": "is in green clothes", "seed": 1729293525285}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Theodora, Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a zebra.", "Ivan isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a cat.", "Peter isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives next door from the one who is owns a snake.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a zebra.", "Theodora lives 2 doors away from Ivan.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Elena?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in yellow clothes", "seed": 1729293526589}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Theodora, Elena.", "Peter is in green clothes.", "Peter lives next door from Theodora.", "Elena is in red clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes also is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "Ivan lives next door from Theodora."], "question": "Who is in yellow clothes?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Peter", "Theodora", "Elena"], "answer": "Theodora", "seed": 1729293527873}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Theodora, Elena.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in yellow clothes.", "Theodora owns a hamster.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also owns a cat.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 2.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a cat."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 4 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a cat", "owns a hamster", "owns a snake"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293528872}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Elena, Peter.", "Elena is at house 3.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a snake.", "Ivan is at house 2.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives next door from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a snake."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Theodora?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293529731}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena, Theodora.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is in blue clothes also is the criminal.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "Elena owns a snake.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 3.", "The person who is at house 3 also is the criminal.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Peter lives next door from Theodora.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives next door from the one who is owns a cat."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["is in yellow clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in green clothes", "seed": 1729293531457}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Theodora, Peter.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a zebra.", "Elena isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "Elena lives 2 doors away from Theodora.", "Ivan owns a snake.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Peter is in red clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes also is the criminal.", "Theodora is at house 3."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["is in yellow clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in red clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293533327}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Peter, Elena.", "Peter isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "Theodora is in blue clothes.", "Theodora lives next door from Elena.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 4.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Theodora.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 4."], "question": "Who is at house 2?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Theodora", "Peter", "Elena"], "answer": "Elena", "seed": 1729293534735}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Elena, Peter.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a zebra.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "Ivan owns a snake.", "Ivan is at house 4.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is at house 4", "is at house 1", "is at house 3", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 2", "seed": 1729293535810}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Ivan, Peter, Theodora.", "Peter owns a snake.", "The person who is owns a snake lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in yellow clothes.", "Peter is in yellow clothes."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 4 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a zebra", "owns a snake", "owns a cat"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293537372}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "One person is a criminal.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a cat.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a hamster.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a cat", "owns a snake", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a snake", "seed": 1729293538462}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a cat.", "Theodora lives next door from Ivan.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in red clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Theodora owns a snake.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a hamster."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a zebra?", "answer_options": ["is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in yellow clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293540499}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a cat.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a snake."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is at house 4", "is at house 1", "is at house 3", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 4", "seed": 1729293541956}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Theodora, Peter, Ivan.", "Ivan is at house 2.", "Elena isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Elena lives next door from Ivan.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in red clothes.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives next door from the one who is is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in green clothes."], "question": "Who is in green clothes?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Theodora", "Peter", "Ivan"], "answer": "Elena", "seed": 1729293543724}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a hamster.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives next door from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in red clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a snake", "owns a zebra", "owns a cat", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a zebra", "seed": 1729293544806}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in yellow clothes.", "Elena is at house 2.", "Peter lives next door from Ivan.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 3."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Ivan?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293545775}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a snake.", "Theodora lives next door from Elena.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "Peter lives next door from Ivan.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 1.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 4.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a snake."], "question": "Who owns a snake?", "answer_options": ["Theodora", "Elena", "Peter", "Ivan"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293547164}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Theodora, Ivan, Elena.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Ivan lives next door from Elena.", "Theodora lives 2 doors away from Ivan.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a snake.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a snake."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in yellow clothes", "seed": 1729293548724}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "People's names are Peter, Theodora, Elena, Ivan.", "Ivan owns a zebra.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Elena owns a snake.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a snake.", "Theodora is in green clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Peter?", "answer_options": ["is in yellow clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in red clothes"], "answer": "is in yellow clothes", "seed": 1729293552487}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Theodora, Peter, Ivan.", "Peter isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "Elena lives next door from Ivan.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also owns a hamster.", "The person who is owns a snake lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 3 also is the criminal.", "Peter isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is the criminal also owns a snake.", "Theodora is at house 2.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a cat."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in green clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a snake", "owns a zebra", "owns a cat", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293553603}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Theodora, Ivan, Elena.", "Elena isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in red clothes.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also is the criminal.", "Theodora lives next door from Ivan.", "Elena is at house 1.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 2.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also owns a zebra.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is at house 4?", "answer_options": ["is in blue clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293554997}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a snake.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Ivan, Theodora, Peter.", "Ivan is at house 2.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a hamster.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives next door from the one who is owns a hamster."], "question": "Who owns a zebra?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Ivan", "Theodora", "Peter"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293556724}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Peter, Elena.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Theodora is at house 1.", "Ivan isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Theodora owns a cat.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a cat.", "Ivan is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in green clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is in red clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in yellow clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293558168}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Theodora, Ivan, Elena.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Ivan is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a cat.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 3.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a zebra."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in yellow clothes", "seed": 1729293559229}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Elena, Peter.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Theodora is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a hamster.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in red clothes.", "The person who is owns a snake lives next door from the one who is owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "Elena is at house 4.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a snake."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a cat", "owns a snake", "owns a zebra", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a zebra", "seed": 1729293560085}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Peter, Elena.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Ivan is at house 3.", "Ivan is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also owns a snake."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who owns a hamster?", "answer_options": ["is at house 3", "is at house 2", "is at house 1", "is at house 4"], "answer": "is at house 2", "seed": 1729293561473}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Ivan, Theodora, Peter.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Theodora is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a snake.", "Ivan owns a hamster.", "Theodora lives 2 doors away from Peter."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a snake", "owns a hamster", "owns a zebra", "owns a cat"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293562655}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena, Theodora.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Theodora.", "Theodora is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is owns a cat lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a hamster.", "Peter owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is in red clothes."], "question": "Which is the house of Elena?", "answer_options": ["is at house 3", "is at house 2", "is at house 4", "is at house 1"], "answer": "is at house 4", "seed": 1729293564115}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a hamster.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a zebra."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 2 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a snake", "owns a hamster", "owns a cat", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a snake", "seed": 1729293565495}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Theodora, Peter.", "Theodora is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "Ivan is in red clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 3.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 1.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Peter.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in blue clothes."], "question": "Which is the house of Elena?", "answer_options": ["is at house 3", "is at house 4", "is at house 2", "is at house 1"], "answer": "is at house 4", "seed": 1729293566948}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a snake.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a cat."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a zebra?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293568291}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 1.", "Peter is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "Ivan lives next door from Elena.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in red clothes."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is in yellow clothes?", "answer_options": ["is at house 4", "is at house 1", "is at house 2", "is at house 3"], "answer": "is at house 2", "seed": 1729293569438}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena, Theodora.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a hamster.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 3.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives next door from the one who is owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a zebra."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in red clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a hamster", "owns a snake", "owns a cat"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293570632}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan, Theodora.", "Elena is at house 3.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in red clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Theodora is at house 4."], "question": "Who is at house 1?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Peter", "Ivan", "Theodora"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293571748}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Theodora, Elena, Ivan.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Peter lives next door from Theodora.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a cat.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a cat.", "Ivan is at house 4."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is at house 2", "is at house 1", "is at house 3", "is at house 4"], "answer": "is at house 4", "seed": 1729293573368}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Elena, Ivan, Theodora.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also owns a snake.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "Elena is at house 3.", "Ivan is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a cat.", "Peter is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in yellow clothes."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in blue clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a zebra", "owns a snake", "owns a cat"], "answer": "owns a zebra", "seed": 1729293575632}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a cat.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a zebra.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "The person who is owns a cat lives next door from the one who is owns a hamster."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a cat", "owns a snake", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a snake", "seed": 1729293577720}
{"facts": ["They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Theodora, Elena, Ivan.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 4.", "Theodora is at house 1.", "Theodora lives next door from Ivan."], "question": "Who is at house 3?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Theodora", "Elena", "Ivan"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293579474}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Theodora, Ivan, Elena.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in green clothes.", "Ivan is in green clothes.", "Theodora lives 2 doors away from Elena."], "question": "Who is in red clothes?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Theodora", "Ivan", "Elena"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293580448}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Peter, Elena.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "Elena is in green clothes.", "Peter lives 2 doors away from Elena.", "Elena is at house 2.", "Peter is in yellow clothes."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is in blue clothes?", "answer_options": ["is at house 3", "is at house 1", "is at house 4", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293581448}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan, Theodora.", "Peter lives 2 doors away from Ivan.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a cat.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 4.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "Theodora owns a zebra.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a snake.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 2.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a cat.", "Elena isn't the person who is in green clothes."], "question": "Who is in blue clothes?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Peter", "Ivan", "Theodora"], "answer": "Elena", "seed": 1729293582603}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena, Theodora.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also owns a hamster.", "Theodora is in red clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Elena lives next door from Theodora.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 3.", "Peter owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in red clothes."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is in blue clothes?", "answer_options": ["is at house 4", "is at house 3", "is at house 2", "is at house 1"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293583780}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Theodora, Peter, Elena, Ivan.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a zebra.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also is the criminal.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a cat."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a snake?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in yellow clothes", "seed": 1729293584766}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Peter, Theodora.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "Theodora is at house 2.", "The person who is in red clothes also is the criminal.", "Elena is the criminal.", "Peter is in yellow clothes.", "Elena lives next door from Peter."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is in green clothes?", "answer_options": ["is at house 1", "is at house 4", "is at house 3", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 1", "seed": 1729293586037}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Theodora, Ivan.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "Elena lives next door from Theodora.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Elena lives next door from Peter.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a snake.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 1.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a zebra."], "question": "Who is in green clothes?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Peter", "Theodora", "Ivan"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293587612}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Theodora, Elena.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in red clothes.", "Peter owns a snake.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Ivan is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a zebra."], "question": "Which is the house of Elena?", "answer_options": ["is at house 3", "is at house 2", "is at house 1", "is at house 4"], "answer": "is at house 4", "seed": 1729293588995}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Theodora, Elena.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena is at house 1.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a cat.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "Peter lives next door from Theodora.", "Ivan is in blue clothes.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in green clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Peter", "Theodora", "Elena"], "answer": "Elena", "seed": 1729293590398}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a zebra.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Theodora, Peter, Ivan.", "Peter lives next door from Ivan.", "Peter is the criminal.", "The person who is the criminal also owns a snake.", "Theodora lives next door from Ivan.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a snake.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 1."], "question": "Which is the house of Elena?", "answer_options": ["is at house 1", "is at house 2", "is at house 4", "is at house 3"], "answer": "is at house 1", "seed": 1729293591656}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Theodora, Elena.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Elena is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a zebra.", "Elena is at house 2.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Elena.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a zebra."], "question": "Who is in yellow clothes?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Ivan", "Theodora", "Elena"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293593026}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 also is the criminal."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 2 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a snake", "owns a hamster", "owns a cat"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293594041}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "Peter lives next door from Elena.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in yellow clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 1.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 2.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a snake."], "question": "What pet does Peter own?", "answer_options": ["owns a cat", "owns a hamster", "owns a snake", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a snake", "seed": 1729293595904}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "Elena owns a snake.", "Peter is in green clothes.", "Peter is at house 4.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a cat."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who owns a hamster?", "answer_options": ["is at house 3", "is at house 2", "is at house 1", "is at house 4"], "answer": "is at house 4", "seed": 1729293597094}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Peter, Elena.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in red clothes.", "Theodora owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Peter owns a zebra.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 2."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 2 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a cat", "owns a zebra", "owns a snake"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1730155284321}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Theodora, Ivan, Peter.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a zebra.", "Theodora is in yellow clothes.", "Peter is at house 3.", "Elena owns a snake.", "Elena lives next door from Peter.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 1."], "question": "Who is in red clothes?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Theodora", "Ivan", "Peter"], "answer": "Elena", "seed": 1730155284886}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a snake.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a hamster.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a cat."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 2 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a cat", "owns a zebra", "owns a snake"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1730155285408}
